https://www.urschel.com/privacy-statement/

×
How Can We Help You?
Phone
By checking this box, I affirm that I have read the Urschel Laboratories, Inc. Privacy Statement and GDPR Consent to Control of Personal Data. I understand my rights of privacy and give consent to Urschel to maintain the personal information I have freely given to it.
Your Contact Information
Your Mailing Information
United States
Africa (Sub-Sahara)
Albania
Algeria
Argentina
Aruba
Australia
Australia (New South Wales)
Austria
Azores
Bahamas
Bahrain
Bangladesh
Belgium (Flemisch)
Belgium (French)
Belize
Bhutan
Bolivia
Bosnia (Northern)
Bosnia (Southern) and Herzegovina
Brazil
Bulgaria
Cambodia
Canada, Alberta and British Columbia
Canada, All Other Provinces
Chile
China
Other
Where did you hear about us?
I'm an Existing Customer
Trade Show
Magazine
Web Search
Other
Your Local Urschel Contact:
Fax:
Territories Covered:
Send
×
Thank You
Thank you for your interest
Privacy Statement
Privacy Statement
Privacy Statement
Urschel Laboratories, Inc. and all of its offices and employees worldwide take the privacy of our customers and vendors seriously.  Please read through our Privacy Statement and be assured that your information will be protected.
Who is covered?
Urschel’s Privacy Policy applies to any person who supplies their personal information, which is collected by Urschel so that we may do business with you.
What information does Urschel collect?
Whether through an online inquiry, or through direct contact with you, Urschel collects and stores personal information from representatives of customers and vendors, including:
First and Last Name;
Business Name and Address;
Business Title;
Email Address;
Phone Number;
Anyone can visit Urschel.com without disclosing any personal information.  If you wish to submit an inquiry to Urschel through our website, you will be asked to review this Policy and provide consent to us receiving the information you alone provide.
How does Urschel use personal information?
Urschel will use personal information that has been provided to:
contact you regarding your inquiry into our products;
provide you with any requested product information;
to provide you with the products and services you request;
Urschel does not receive personal information from third-party marketing services, through public records, or through other organizations.  Also, Urschel does not share the personal information of our customers and vendors with any third-party without your consent to do so.
Urschel does not use cookies.
Urschel does not receive any personal information through its use of Google Analytics.
What can I do about my personal information being stored?
If you do not want Urschel to keep your personal information, you may request that we delete it. You may also request that Urschel provide you with what personal information we have, how it is stored, and for it to be corrected if there are any mistakes.
How is my information being protected?
Urschel’s primary aim is to make sure our customers’ and vendors’ information is safe from data breaches. We have security measures in place to keep your information protected and will promptly notify you if your data may have been accessed by unauthorized persons or entities, has been improperly disclosed or used, has been improperly maintained, or has been modified or deleted. All Urschel employees worldwide value your privacy and have a responsibility to safeguard your data.
Who do I contact about my personal information?
If you have any questions about how Urschel ensures your privacy, what personal information we may store, questions about having your personal data deleted or corrected, or generally about Urschel’s ability to protect your personal data, you may contact us directly at  privacy@urschel.com.
Data Protection Officers:  Eric Buss, Urschel Laboratories, Inc.; Richard Cranefield, Urschel International Ltd.; Megan Pikula, Urschel Laboratories, Inc.;
Urschel Laboratories, Inc.
1200 Cutting Edge Drive
Chesterton, IN 46304, U.S.A.
Email: privacy@urschel.com
Website: www.Urschel.com/privacy-statement/
v. 8
Trademark Information
® Urschel, Affinity, Affinity Integra, Comitrol, Comitrol logo design, DiversaCut, DiversaCut logo designs, DiversaCut 2110, DiversaCut 2110A, DiversaCut SPRINT, Flat-V, QuantiCut, QuantiCut logo design, TranSlicer, TranSlicer logo designs, TranSlicer 2000, TranSlicer 2500, MicroSlice, Velocicut, Velocicut logo design, Urschel housemark symbol, Flo-Cut (U.S.A. only), Urschalloy, The Global Leader in Food Cutting Technology, and Urschel the Size Reduction Specialists logo are all registered trademarks of Urschel Laboratories, Inc.  ™MicroAdjustable pending. All rights reserved.
Copyright © 2014, Urschel Laboratories, Inc. All rights reserved. All text, images, graphics, animation, videos, music, sounds, and other materials on this website ("site") are subject to the copyrights and other intellectual property rights of Urschel Laboratories, Inc., its affiliated companies, and its licensors. Urschel Laboratories, Inc. owns the copyrights in the selection, coordination, and arrangement of the materials on this site. These materials may not be copied for commercial use or distribution, nor may these materials be modified or reposted to other sites.
Our Most Popular Machines
Affinity® Integra-D DicerTranSlicer® 2520 CutterAffinity Integra® DicerAFFINITY® DicersModel CC-D ShredderModel CC-DL ShredderModel CCX-D ShredderDiversaCut 2110A® DicerDiversaCut Sprint® DicerE TranSlicer® CutterModel CC SlicerModel M6 DicerComitrol® Processor Model 1700Comitrol® Processor Models 3600 - 3675SLComitrol® Processor Model 9300Model N GranulatorModel RA-A DicerSprint 2® Dicer
